http://imaginethatinc.com/13-about/67-privacypolicy

HomeProductsExtendSim ProductsProduct OverviewExtendSim CPExtendSim DEExtendSim Pro
• Rate Technology
• Reliability Block Diagramming in ExtendSimTry ExtendSimTry ExtendSim CPTry ExtendSim DETry ExtendSim ProFeaturesAbout ExtendSimExtendSim FeaturesNew Features in ExtendSim 10AdvantagesExtendSim InnovationsExtendSim AdvantagesEvolution of ExtendSimWhich one do I buy?ExtendSim Product AdvisorTypes of ExtendSim LicensesUser TypesPurchasing InfoPricingMaintenance & Support PlanUpgrade to ExtendSim 10Request QuoteSolutionsSimulationSimulation DefinedWhy ExtendSim?Modeling MethodologiesIndustriesBusiness & ServiceChemical Engineering, Mining, & Process FlowsCommunication NetworksDefense, Military, & Security Systems ModelingFood & BeveragesGovernment & Public SectorHealthcareLogistics, Supply Chains, & TransportationManufacturingPandemic Response ManagementReliability EngineeringSustainability & Environmental ModelingPublicationsPapersBooksExtendSim DocumentationSpotlightAwards & SponsorshipsSupportInstalling & ActivatingIndividualNode-LockedFloatingTry ExtendSimTry ExtendSim CPTry ExtendSim DETry ExtendSim ProUpdating ExtendSimLearning CenterGetting Started with ExtendSimQuickTipsMicroLearning QuickCoachGetting to Know ExtendSimModel Building TemplatesSample ModelsTransitioning from ExtendSim 9 to 10ExtendSim DocumentationTrainingCoursesRegisterAuthorized TrainersSystem RequirementsFAQsContact ExtendSim SupportResourcesGlobal ResellersConsultantsExpert Solutions ProvidersExtendSim DocumentationSocial NetworkingAcademicPrograms & PricingAdopter ProgramAdopter SchoolsApply for Adopter ProgramUpdate Adopter StatusResearch GrantsResearch Grants In ProgressResearch Grants FulfilledResearch Grant ApplicationUpdate a Research GrantShowcaseTextbooksExtendSim for Discrete-Event System SimulationOther BooksContact UsExtendSim Store
Privacy
Protecting your privacy is important to Imagine That Inc. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.
Why we collect personal information
Imagine That! uses your personal information only with your permission to give you superior customer service and to provide you with convenient access to our products and support services. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and other information we think you would like to hear about. This may occasionally include information from other technology companies about products and services that can add value to your Imagine That! products. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products.
How we collect personal information
We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service, register to attend a seminar, or participate in an online survey. In addition, when you register a new Imagine That! product, sign up for Imagine That! support services, or ask to be included in an email mailing list, we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database.
When you fill out a form on our web site (e.g. to download a Trial version of ExtendSim, upgrade your copy of ExtendSim, etc.) the information you provide us will only be used to either send you the information you have requested, track information about downloads from our web site, update our registration database, or monitor our customer's use of the web as an upgrade medium. If you do not wish to be contacted from the information you provide us on this web site, please let us know your preferences.
Imagine That! works with other companies that help us provide products and services to you, and we may provide your personal information to these companies. For example, we give shipping companies this information so they can deliver your products efficiently. The information they receive is for shipping and delivery purposes only, and we require that the companies safeguard your personal information in accordance with our policies.
How we protect your personal information
Imagine That! safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.
Collecting other personal information
When you browse our web site, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse - not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.
Like many web sites, the Imagine That! web site uses "cookie" technology. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our web sites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.
In some of our emails to you, we use a "click-through URL." When you click one of these URL's, you pass through our web server before arriving at the web site that is your destination. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.
Our company wide commitment to privacy
To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every Imagine That, Inc. employee.
Imagine That!'s web site contains links to other sites. Imagine That! does not share your personal information with those web sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.
The Imagine That! Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
